

# Subhan Ikraam Haidar

Software Engineer

+62 85159422131



haidar.dod@gmail.com



Karangwaru, Sleman, D.I.Y

A final year Information Systems student with a focus on web and mobile programming. Experienced in building web applications using PHP and the Laravel framework, and capable of developing Android mobile applications using the Flutter framework. Able to work independently and as part of a team, and possesses good communication and problem-solving skills. Excited to start a career and contribute to the development of innovative and useful applications.



https://github.com/haidar-jpr



https://www.linkedin.com/in/subhan-ikraam-haidar/



https://haidar-jpr.github.io/personal-portfolio/

# **Project Experience**

## Final College Assignment Project

2024 -present

## **Decision Support System**

This project is a final lecture assignment which is used as one of the student graduation requirements, where here I continue the previous project application by adding decision support system features.

- Developed using PHP programming language, Laravel Framework, and MySQL DBMS.
- Used to facilitate and accelerate the process of determining assistants.
- · The feature offered is the use of the profiler matching method to help determine which applicants have the best ranking as a decision support.

#### **Practical Work Project**

2023 - 2024

## Web-based Application for Laboratory Course Assistant Registration

This project is a course assignment that requires students to produce a simple application product.

- Developed natively using the PHP programming language and MySQL DBMS.
- Used to facilitate the registration of laboratory course assistants.
- · The features offered include laboratory assistant registration, easy management of applicant data, printing reports, announcing announcements, and determining whether or not students are accepted.

### **Build With Angga Course Project**

2023 - 2024

#### Full-Stack Web Developer: Toko Online

Making aplication based on course.

## Education

#### **Bachelor of Information Systems**

2020 - present

#### University of Technology Yogyakarta

Current GPA: 3.83

#### Bangsri 1 State High School

2017 - 2020

#### Bangsri 1 State High School

Focuses on the science.

# **Expertise**

Design Figma (basic using) Source Code Management Git

Programming Languages PHP, Dart, Java Operating System Windows, Linux

Database Firebase (basic), MySQL Others Team work,

Problem-Solving, Proactive Attitude

API RESTful APIs

## Organization & Activity ------

Assistant Professor Algorithms & Data Structures · Sep 2023 - Jan 2024

I help lecturers teach the technical practice section for Algorithms & Data Structures courses.

- Helping students to solve their error.
- Help assess students' every projects.
- Teach material according to the module provided.

Assistant Professor Object-Oriented Programming · Sep 2023 - Jan 2024

I help lecturers teach the technical practice section for Object-oriented programming courses.

- Helping students to solve their error.
- Help assess students' final projects.
- Teach material according to the module provided.

Assistant Professor Web Service Practice · Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

I help lecturers teach the technical practice section for web service courses.

- Helping students to solve their error.
- Help assess students' final projects.
- Teach material according to the module provided.

Scout Organizational activity planner · Jun 2019 - Jun 2020

In this organization my job is to create and arrange a schedule for extracurricular activities that are held every week as well as events that will be carried out by the school. In addition, he is also responsible for the continuity of the ongoing event so that it runs smoothly as planned. And if things happen that are not desirable, it will be improvised right away or as a lesson in the future.

# Languages

Indonesia Native Speaker

**English** Professional work only